https://www.germanshepherdrescue.co.uk/german-shepherd-rescue-privacy-policy-i-502.html?osCsid=e41cfa6228cb8de198f532d0a19b5394

Go Top
Menu
HomepageAbout usAbout GSDRPhilosophical BeliefsAbout The BreedAdoptionAdoption/Foster FormCaucasian ShepherdsContact UsDogs For RehomingUrgent DogsDogs In KennelsOlder German ShepherdsNorth East DogsNorth West DogsCentral DogsEastern DogsSouth East DogsSouth West DogsDogs in WalesGerman Shepherd CrossesCaucasian ShepherdsHonorary Shepherd DogsDogs We Have RehomedDog trainingFAQsHelp support usNatural HealthAnal FurunculosisAutoimmune DiseasesCancer Cures and PreventionCanine CataractsDM (CDRM)Fleas Ticks Mites WormsGastrointestinal ProblemsNatural Cleaning and WashingNatural Health ArticlesNatural Healthy DietNatural Health RemediesSkin Problems & AllergiesVaccination or NosodesNews and ArticlesLatest NewsArticles and StoriesEvents and FundraisingPicture GalleryPuppies and BreedersRehome Your DogShopHats and CapsHoodies, Jackets, FleecesOther Nice ThingsT-shirtsChildrens ClothingDogmatic Headcollars & LeadsSuccess StoriesVolunteer FormWalk GroupsUrgent Dogs
HomepageAbout usAbout GSDRPhilosophical BeliefsAbout The BreedAdoptionAdoption/Foster FormCaucasian ShepherdsContact UsDogs For RehomingUrgent DogsDogs In KennelsOlder German ShepherdsNorth East DogsNorth West DogsCentral DogsEastern DogsSouth East DogsSouth West DogsDogs in WalesGerman Shepherd CrossesCaucasian ShepherdsHonorary Shepherd DogsDogs We Have RehomedDog trainingFAQsHelp support usNatural HealthAnal FurunculosisAutoimmune DiseasesCancer Cures and PreventionCanine CataractsDM (CDRM)Fleas Ticks Mites WormsGastrointestinal ProblemsNatural Cleaning and WashingNatural Health ArticlesNatural Healthy DietNatural Health RemediesSkin Problems & AllergiesVaccination or NosodesNews and ArticlesLatest NewsArticles and StoriesEvents and FundraisingPicture GalleryPuppies and BreedersRehome Your DogShopHats and CapsHoodies, Jackets, FleecesOther Nice ThingsT-shirtsChildrens ClothingDogmatic Headcollars & LeadsSuccess StoriesVolunteer FormWalk GroupsUrgent Dogs
German Shepherd Dog Rescue Privacy policy
From the 25th May 2018 the General Data Protection Regulation will come into effect. This new regulation is designed to keep your personal information safer and we are committed to following the new rules.Why do we need a Privacy Policy?Our privacy policy lets you know what information is being collected, how it is being used and why.German Shepherd Dog Rescue (GSDR) is a breed specific dog rescue charity that rescues dogs across the UK but mainly England and Wales. We are registered with the Charities Commission, Registered Charity Number 1141122. We are also a not for profit company registered with Companies House, registration number 06669864.GSDR is committed to protecting your privacy.What information do we collect and how is it collected?If you fill in one of our website forms to volunteer for GSDR, to adopt or foster a dog or to rehome your dog, we will collect basic information about you which includes your name, postal address, email address, telephone number, and then information on your home, lifestyle and experience with the German Shepherd breed.If you donate or make a payment to us via our website, we will collect basic information which includes your name and email address and our third party payment processors will collect your payment information. If you agree to Gift Aid or you are purchasing an item from our shop, we will also collect your home address, so we can claim the Gift Aid or post items out to you. Virgin Money Giving collects all the information required to allocate Gift Aid to GSDR.When you visit our website, we use Google Analytics to log information and details of visitor behaviour. This doesn’t identify individuals, it just helps us to find out information about traffic to our website such as how many people have visited our website and which pages they visited.What do we do with the information that you give us?We will only use your information to contact you regarding suitable dogs to foster or adopt, volunteering or rehoming your dog.We will use your information to process any payments or orders you have made and claim any Gift Aid, where applicable.How long do we keep the information you give us?We will not keep any of your information longer than necessary. If you adopt a dog from us, we will keep your information on file for the life of the dog. If you rehome your dog via us, we will keep your information on file for the life of the dog in case we need to contact you regarding the dog’s history.If you foster or volunteer for us will keep your information on file as long as you remain an active volunteer.We will keep information on any payments made to us in accordance with the law regarding financial record keeping and Gift Aid claims. We will keep any other personal information you have shared with us for no longer than 90 days, unless you have explicitly consented to us contacting you further.How do we share, store, protect and process your information? We will not sell or pass on your personal information to others. Your information will be securely stored and access restricted. We will only pass your information to one of our trusted volunteers to carry out a home check or assess your dog for rehoming.We may use service providers who provide IT and system administration services to process and store data, such as web hosting, email services and database storage. These providers are compliant with the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) and based in the EEA, in countries recognised as providing adequate data protection by The European Commission or are in the US but are part of the EU-US Privacy Shield Framework.What are your rights?In accordance with UK and European law under the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) you have the right to view, amend or delete any of the personal information that we hold about you.Policy Updated: 9th May 2018
Please help support the rescue
Please help us by making a donation so that we can help re home more unwanted German Shepherd Dogs. Donations can be sent to Jayne Shenstone, German Shepherd Rescue, Little Vauld, Marden Hereford HR1 3HA.
Thank you.
© German Shepherd Rescue 2020
Registered in England and Wales as company number 06669864 Registered Charity Number 1141122German Shepherd Rescue, Little Vauld, Marden Hereford HR1 3HA.German Shepherd Rescue helping rehome GSD's
GSDR Privacy policy
